www.linkedin.com/in/Tony-Magrady

Summary

IT project manager / project coordinator in application development and migration, security and data privacy. Accomplished project manager employing IT experience to support corporate objectives for 15+ years, and employing PMI project methodology as a certified PMP for the last two-plus years. Experience in utility, financial, software-provider, and manufacturing industries as a full-time employee and a consultant.

Roles: Project manager, project coordinator, project and departmental budgeting, procurement, contractual review, team leadership, and application development.

Experience

Ameri100 / Pace Harmon with client Brunswick, Rosemont, IL

2019 - Current

Mobile: (312) 296-3486

IT Project Coordinator / IT Project Manager

Joined Lumos Cloud Migration project in progress, to provide project and administrative support to Deployment team in charge of monthly releases to the cloud. Adopted new progress measurement methods and KPI reporting standards to renew focus and program management visibility to risks, problem areas, and challenged resource teams. Refined my skills with tools such as Microsoft Project, Excel, and Azure DevOps in support of the above.

Brunswick - Life Fitness Lumos Cloud Migration

- Prepared the project schedule and status reports for monthly application releases to Oracle OCI and Microsoft Azure clouds as laaS / PaaS, as member of Deployment oversight team.
- Created, maintained and presented to program management the detailed application status reports showing all migration lifecycle phases.
- Assisted Lumos Project Management team with MS Project data synchronization with Azure DevOps detailed schedule, and became Lumos MS Project administrator.

DFIN Solutions, Downers Grove, IL

2017 - 2019

IT Project Manager / IT Project Coordinator

On point to lead security, privacy, governance, and enterprise-level projects. Was part of a project management team that built the DFIN Project Management Office to establish project and portfolio standards and develop supporting tools.

Atlassian Confluence Installation and Configuration

- Implemented Atlassian Confluence Data Center for internal DFIN Solutions use in Microsoft Azure as IaaS.
- Developed and tracked to project schedule with internal team and reseller / consultant Herzum. Coordinated schedules and anticipated planned and unplanned resource unavailability.
- Adopted all infrastructure standards and production change management requirements into the project on a platform that was new to the organization - laaS in Azure.

Project Management Office (PMO) Creation

- Collaborated with the organizational manager and other project managers to create the first informal Project
 Management Office at DFIN. Sent RFIs to / received demonstrations from several portfolio, resource, and project
 management vendors, and selected Smartsheet.
- Created and refined a project stage gating process to define all required pre-phase checks and approval for projects. Also created project sizing and prioritization tools, to be used by the Executive Steering Committee.

Data Privacy Projects

- Created a bi-weekly steering committee summary of Data Privacy Programs using team metrics provided by the operational manager. Maintained a Data Privacy Roadmap of the data privacy direction and strategy for the organization, which was enhanced in preparation for periodic executive meetings.
- Prepared for General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of the European Union, effective May 2018. Led
 initiatives in preparation for GDPR, including comprehensive personal data inventory / mapping, oversight of thirdparty contract language update for GDPR, and publication of the corporate Privacy Notice in several languages.

Vulnerability Management and Penetration Testing Program

- Created monthly vulnerability management reports and asset protection and logging agent reports that summarized asset vulnerability counts and inactive server agents by data center and support team.
- Led initiative to have Rapid7 Nexpose tool authenticate into assets in order to fully report vulnerabilities.
- Created formal procedure for engagement with and operational testing and remediation with third party penetration testers (pen testing). Tracked and reported pen testing progress and remediation weekly.

Peoples Energy - WEC Energy Group, Chicago, IL

1998 - 2016

IT Project Manager / IT Project Coordinator at Peoples Energy - Team Lead at WEC

Leader of CIS application support team of direct reports and Accenture off shore consultants. Delivered and supported Accenture Open-cIS customer application serving Wisconsin Public Service, Michigan Gas Utilities, and Minnesota Energy Resources - three utilities of WEC. Earlier, effectively managed customer and workforce management application projects at Peoples Energy and Integrys.

Open-cIS Go-Live for WEC Wisconsin, Minnesota, and Michigan utilities

- Implemented Accenture Open-cIS customer application at three of WEC call centers and utilities for service orders and device management.
- Effectively transitioned team from project development into production support mode. Assigned roles based on supported project functionality and technical skills, and to address several critical support issues at Go-Live.
- Projected \$3 Million in annual corporate savings by 2018 through consolidating to Open-cIS across utilities.

Request for Proposal and selection for mobile data component of asset management application

- Created proposal document for three selected vendors identifying required system and functional specifications, delivery timeline, and corporate policies for vendor contracts.
- Reviewed all proposals with business representatives and legal department and received suggestions for updates. Weighed vendor / product qualifications and ease of integration with asset system.
- Selection of Logica RT-Mobile saved significant labor costs, replacing antiquated paper ticket process, and best satisfied integration requirements.

Annual IT Budget Preparation

- Forecasted two-year expenses on supported software (ex. Advantex mobile application) and supporting software (ex. MicroFocus COBOL). Factored in planned projects, support needs, expected change in software usage, license types, and capital versus operational expenses.
- Responsible for combined budget of \$425,000 after annual price increases of five percent.

Accelerated Main Replacement Program (AMRP) - S2K Customer Application

- Led project to integrate Logica asset management system to PwC S2K customer application.
- Ensured \$400,000 in annual Service department labor of the AMRP functionality that flowed through Advantex mobile data application was properly capitalized by creating new capital job codes and by automating the upload into the accounting system.
- Improved customer satisfaction and increased operational efficiency greatly by automating in-ground facility status and work order updates real time.

Inside Safety Inspection Event Process - Dashboard and Batch Scheduling

- Replaced a system created by Compliance area which included daily manual process by IT development team, labor-intensive for both areas. Saved approximately \$11,000 per month in on-going labor for both areas together.
- Created a dashboard to generate, control, and monitor regulatory inside safety inspection orders for 850,000 customers every three years. Integrated with nightly batch letter and order generation.
- Enhanced tracking and reporting of remaining inspections by geographic area, thus reducing risk of IL State Commission fines for less than 100% compliance.

Professional Tools and Products

Project Management, Collaboration, Productivity: Microsoft SharePoint, Teams, Confluence, Smartsheet,

Microsoft Project, Microsoft Excel / Office

Azure DevOps, Visual Studio Microsoft IDEs:

Languages and Databases: SQL Server, Oracle, Visual Basic, XML, Legacy languages

Self-Study in Process: SAP S/4HANA

Education

Loyola University - Chicago, IL Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Major Computer Science Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Science Loyola University - Chicago, IL

MicroTrain - Lombard, IL Project Management Professional (PMP Certified) MicroTrain - Lombard, IL Lean Six Sigma Green Belt (LSSGB Certified)

Joliet Junior College - Joliet, IL National Career Readiness Certificate (NCRC) Gold